# Find all the errors in this program and correct them. The program should be error free and run without any issues.
    #"""Determine if user choice is on the menu. Returns `True` if it is else return `False`"""
    #"""Return the cost for a given menu item."""
# Ask the user what they would like to eat
# Print the choice and the cost
# Create a temperature converter program that takes input from a user in Fahrenheit and converts it to Celsius. 
#Shubham Chandra
#Problem 1
# You should check that the input is valid (ie. the input is a positive, whole number). 
# If it is not, warn the user to enter a whole number, positive number and exit the program.  
# If it is a valid number, print the temperature rounded to two decimal places.
#Shubham Chandra
#Problem 2
# consulted https://stackoverflow.com/questions/5424716/how-can-i-check-if-string-input-is-a-number     
#Shubham Chandra
#Problem 3
#check if the string is equal to or longer than 12 char
#check it has a lower case letter
#check if string has numeber in it
#check that string has upper case in it
#Check that string has a special character in it
#get password
#check against all conditions
#Shubham Chandra
#Problem 4
# Implement a function that takes three numbers as input and returns the largest of the three. 
# While there is a built-in function max() in Python, do not use it.
#Shubham Chandra
#Problem 5 
#To determine divisibility by 11, take the alternating sum of the digits in the number, read from left to right. 
# If that sum is divisible by 11, so is the original number.
# example: 123 > 1 - 2 + 3
#Shubham Chandra
#problem 6
#A palindrome is a word, phrase, or sequence that reads the same backward as forward. For example, mom , racecar , "never odd or even", and "do geese see god" are all palindromes.
#Write a program that prompts a user to enter a word or phrase and test if it is a palindrome. Ignore any spaces when evaulating the strings.
#Shubham Chandra
#problem 7
#Write a function that draws a triangle out of asterix similar to that below. The function should take an integer argument that represents the height of the triangle. Do not use a recursive function.
#Shubham Chandra
# Problem 8
# Write a Rock-Papers-Scissors game where a user plays against the computer.
#The program should ask the user to choose an object and then compare to a randomly generated object from the computer. 
#If the objects are the same, then play again. If the objects are different the winner is chosen from the following rules:
#The program should always ask if the player would like to play again. Use the following games as an example:
# try recreating this with another function to display winner text 
